buffzone.com 2007-12-23

# Privacy Policy & Agreement : News : Boulder Daily Camera

Prairie Mountain Publishing Company Copyright, Privacy Policy & User Agreement

DailyCamera.com, BroomfieldEnterprise.com, and Buffzone.com are committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the web will not only protect consumers, but also increase consumer confidence and ultimately their participation in online. At DailyCamera.com, BroomfieldEnterprise.com, and Buffzone.com we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. 

The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our sites, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. 

Our sites may contain links to other web sites, including web sites directed to children. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our sites. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the web site sponsor when linking to other web sites. 

## I. Information Which We Collect

We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address, postal address, home or work telephone number, credit card number (only if you choose to purchase a product online), for purposes such as correspondence, making a purchase, or participating in online contests, surveys or games. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. 

Like many other commercial sites, our sites may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a web site recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. Our web sites may use cookies to enhance your visit. Cookies can securely store a user's password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections, such as those selected in a "shopping cart." Our cookies may collect your domain name and track your selections through our web pages. We only use "cookies" to gather the information indicated in this policy and do not use cookies to gather personal identifying information about you without your consent. 

We also use cookies in connection with our chat rooms in order to record your preferences. These cookies store automatically information pertaining to the last chat room you visited, as well as certain comments that can be issues in the chat room, in order to facilitate your experience with the chat rooms. No additional identifying information is stored on these cookies. You also have the option of choosing to allow us to use a cookie to store your username, or "handle" and password on your computer for use in that chat rooms, forums and other sites as indicated on the particular site.

We may require you to supply us with personal information (demographic information such as average age, income, education, population data, zip codes) during a "registration" process online prior to using certain features of our site. For example, you may be required to register to use chat rooms, forums, to access archival stories, to subscribe to newspapers, and to access other features. We use this general information to aggregate information according to demographics, such as gender, geographic location, age, income or a combination of these or other demographics.

Like many other commercial sites, our sites may utilize an electronic file called a web beacon to count users who have visited a page or recognize users by accessing certain cookies. Our site and/or our partner web sites use web beacons in the following way:

* For auditing purposes and to collect information from the websites of certain partners. 

* Information recorded through these web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users from our partners. Aggregate information may include demographic and usage information. No personally identifiable information about you is shared with partners. 

Our practice is to require our partners to disclose the presence of these web beacons on their pages in their privacy policies and state what choices are available to users regarding the collection and use of this information. You may choose to opt-out by contacting us at the e-mail address, postal address or telephone number stated above.

In addition, users may complete a subscription form online in order to subscribe to the Daily Camera and Broomfield Enterprise. To [subscribe,](http://www.dailycamera.com/subscribe) users must submit personal information in order for us to send the newspaper to you. 

## II. Use of User Information 

We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior. This allows us to measure relative consumer interest in the various areas of our web sites for product development purposes. Any information we collect is used for its own internal purposes to improve the content of the web sites, to enhance users' experiences when visiting our sites, to customize the content and/or layout of our pages, and to provide the services required by an individual user. We do not use personal identifying information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this Policy or at the time the information is requested. We never send e-mail to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by e-mail. There are instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about the site or our advertisers to your e-mail address, but this will be done only with your permission and consent 

## III. Disclosure to Third Parties

We do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or other business partners. In some instances, we operate shared web sites with businesses affiliated with us. Our privacy policy will apply to these web sites, and our affiliates adhere to our privacy policy and will not share personal information with any third party without your permission. PLEASE BE AWARE that when you voluntarily disclose personal information (such as your name, e-mail address) in chat areas or bulletin boards to third parties, that information may be collected by others outside the control of us and may result in unsolicited messages from others. 

## IV. Accuracy of User Information 

Questions regarding our privacy policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of the information collected should be directed via e-mail at [webmaster@dailycamera.com.com](mailto:webmaster@dailycamera.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question), or you can reach us by telephone at 303-466-3636. You can also write us at:

DailyCamera.com and BroomfieldEnterprise.com   
PO Box 591  
Boulder, CO 80306 

These privacy policies are effective as of April 19, 2005. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect.

## V. Security of Information 

We use our best efforts to ensure the security of personal information submitted by users. When collecting credit card information for online purchases, we offer secured-server transactions that encrypt your information in transit to thwart someone from intercepting it and misusing it. When we collect other information from our users, it is stored in an area where the general public does not have access to it. 

## VI. Opting-out 

At any time while assessing our site(s), any user while online may "opt-out" of further e-mail contact from us (while still allowing access to our sites). For further information about opting-out, contact us at the e-mail address, postal address or telephone number stated above. 

## VII. Use of Materials

The right to download and store or output the materials in our sites is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on these sites may contact us.

## USER AGREEMENT 

All materials on this site ©1999 – 2007 Prairie Mountain Publishing Co. or used with permission. All rights reserved.

DailyCamera.com, BroomfieldEnterprise.com, and Buffzone.com are registered trademarks of the Company.

**Terms of Use**

Use of this site signifies your agreement with the following terms of use. If you do not agree with any of these terms of use, please do not use this site. The Prairie Mountain Publishing Co. (the "Company") reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify these Terms of Use at any time and you agree to be bound by such modifications through your use of the Company’s site. The Company may require you to register and provide certain information to it as a condition of using or accessing certain features, functions and content.

## TRADEMARKS, COPYRIGHTS & RESTRICTIONS

All materials on this site, including, but not limited to, images, illustrations, audio clips, video clips (the "Materials") are protected by copyrights which are owned or licensed by the Company. DailyCamera.com, BroomfieldEnterprise.com, and Buffzone.com are trademarks of the Company. You may not reproduce, perform, create derivative works from, republish, upload, post, transmit, or distribute in any way whatsoever any Materials from www.dailycamera.com, www.buffzone.com or any other web site owned or operated by the Company without the prior written permission of the Company. However, you may download or make one copy of the Materials, and other downloadable items displayed on the site, for personal non-commercial home use only consistent with the purpose for which the Materials are made available by the Company, provided all copyright and other notices contained in the Materials are left intact. Any modification of the Materials, or any portion thereof, or use of the Materials for any other purpose constitutes an infringement of the Company’s copyrights and other proprietary rights. Use of these Materials on any other web site or other networked computer environment, whether by way of copying the Materials or by linking to them, is prohibited without prior written permission from the Company.

## SUBMISSIONS

Copyright on materials contributed by **Prairie Mountain Publishing Co.** readers and/or members is held by the individual creators.

All postings, messages, text, files, images, graphics, photos, audio clips, sounds, video or other materials (the "Content") posted on, transmitted through, or linked from the Site, are the sole responsibility of the person from whom such Content originated. You are entirely responsible for all Content that you post, e-mail or otherwise make available through the Site. For all Content provided by you, you agree to indemnify Provider as provided below.

By uploading or otherwise posting any Content on the Site, you represent and warrant: (i) you own or otherwise have all necessary rights, including but not limited to copyrights, to the content you provide and the rights to use it as provided in this Terms of Service; (ii) all information you provide is true, accurate, current and complete, and does not violate these Terms of Service; and, (iii) the content will not cause injury to any person or entity.

You agree not to upload, transmit, distribute or otherwise publish in these or any other Forums connected with the Company any Materials which are:

off topic, personal attacks, libelous, defamatory, obscene, abusive, pornographic, threatening, or an invasion of privacy;   
an infringement of the intellectual property rights, including, but not limited to, copyrights and trademarks, of any person or entity;   
illegal in any way or which advocate illegal activity;   
an advertisement or solicitation of funds, goods, or services.

You agree not to impersonate anyone else or pass yourself off as someone else, including the Camera or public figures.

The Site does not tolerate [sock puppeting](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sockpuppeting) \- controlling multiple accounts with intent to mislead.

**License**

For all such information and material, you grant **Prairie Mountain Publishing Co,** its affiliates and related entities, and its affiliated newspaper, a royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive right and license to use, copy, modify, display, archive, store, distribute, reproduce and create derivative works from such information, in any form, media, software or technology of any kind now existing or developed in the future.

**No Pre-Screening or Editing**

This site offers weblogs, forums, photo galleries and other interactive areas where users can express opinions and share ideas and information. Prairie Mountain Publishing Co cannot and does not monitor all of the material posted or transmitted to the Site. Additionally, the Company does not control, and is not responsible for, Content made available through the Site by members.

By using the Site, you may be exposed to Content that you may find offensive, indecent, inaccurate, misleading, or otherwise objectionable. You agree that you must evaluate, and bear all risks associated with, the use of the Site and any of its Content, including but not limited to whether you should rely on said Content. 

You also agree that under no circumstances will Prairie Mountain Publishing Co. or its affiliates be liable in any way for any Content or for any loss or damage of any kind incurred as a result of the use of any Content posted, emailed or otherwise made available via the Site. You acknowledge that Provider does not pre-screen or approve Content, but that the Company shall have the right (but not the obligation) in its sole discretion to refuse, delete or move any Content that is available via the Site, for violating the letter or spirit of the Terms or for any other reason. The Company reserves the right to delete any posting, message or photograph at any time, for any reason or no reason.

## TERMINATION

The Company may, in its sole discretion, terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the site, including, but not limited to, any bulletin boards on its site, for any reason, including without limitation, breach of this agreement. In the event this agreement is terminated, the restrictions regarding Materials appearing on the site, and the representations and warranties, indemnities, and limitations of liabilities set forth in this agreement shall survive any such termination.

## JURISDICTION

This site is controlled and operated by the Company from the Company’s headquarters in Boulder, Colorado. The Company does not represent or warrant that Materials on the site are appropriate or available for use in other locations. If you choose to access this site from other locations, you do so at your own risk and are responsible for compliance with any and all local laws.

This agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Colorado, as it is applied to agreements entered into and performed within that State. Any action brought to enforce this agreement or matters related to the site shall be brought in either the State or Federal Courts of Colorado. If any provision of this agreement is deemed void, unlawful or otherwise unenforceable for any reason, that provision shall be severed from this agreement and the remaining provisions of this agreement shall remain in force. This contains the entire agreement between you and the Company concerning your use of the site.
